Okay, let's get...
Okay, let's get started.
So the first website I want to show you is Exorcism.
My personal opinion is that this website is structured in a beginner friendly way.
So if you want to deep your toes into the rust programming language, but you don't want
to go too deep too fast, I would strongly recommend it.
This website features a variety of different programming languages with which you can get
started with.
And personally I would say it has a really nice, clean UI.
Maybe one of the issues that I found is that there aren't enough exercises for the rust
programming language.
But maybe that will be added and changed in the future.